A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Eliza L. C. Smith to "Mamie"; "Lelia" 1878 Jan. 7 & April 23, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 Jan. 28; Feb. 17 & 24, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 Jan. 29, 2 ALS, 1 AL (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter, Lelia M. Smith (Mrs. Lucian Cocke) 1878 Jan. 29; Feb. 12; April 6, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Rosalie Harrison Thornton 1878 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to brother-in-law J. Howard Smith 1878 Feb. 4, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eleanor (Ellie) Smith 1878 Feb. 5 & 14, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- E. L. C. Smith to sister, Eleanor A. Smith 1878 Feb. 5; March 21; April 3, 25, & 28, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor A. Smith (later 1. Mrs. Fielding Miles, 2. Mrs. Charles Kent) 1878 Feb. 5; March 26; April 10, 4 ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 Feb. 9; March 14; May 30, 3 ALS (Box 19)
- Daniel G. Smith to J. Howard Smith 1878 Feb. 9, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1878 Feb. 11, APCS (Box 19)
- F[rancis] H. Smith to J. Howard Smith 1878 Feb. 12, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to [Ellen and Daniel G. Smith] 1878 Feb. 18 & Aug. 15, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza Lewis Smith 1878 Feb. 21, ALS (Box 19)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to Lucy R. Harrison 1878 March 12, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Lelia M. Smith 1878 March 14; April 3; May 3, 3 ALS (Box 19)
- Francis Harrison Smith to his daughter, Eleanor A. Smith (later 1. Mrs. Fielding D. Miles 2. Mrs. Charlie W. Kent) 1878 March 28, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter Lelia M. Smith (Mrs. Lucian Cocke); Sketch of her sister Maria's character 1878 March 28, AL (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1878 May 6, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1878 May 6, ALS (Box 19)
- Emma Rogers to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 May 16, ALS (Box 19)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1878 May 16, ALS (Box 19)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton and William M. Thornton to Miss Lelia M. Smith 1878 May 19 & 29, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Lelia Smith 1878 May 23, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to sister, Eleanor S. Smith 1878 June 6; Dec. 2, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- [Eliza Smith Walker] to father, Francis Harrison Smith 1878 June 7, AL (fragment) (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 June 14 & Nov. 7, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Daniel G. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1878 June 14, ALS (Box 19)
- Charles C. Harrison to E. L. C. 1878 July 29, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1878 July 31; Sept. 14 & 16; Oct. 18; Nov. 22, 5 ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to grandmother, Mrs. E. L. C. Harrison 1878 Aug. 23; Sept. 20; Oct. 21, 3 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1878 Aug.23, 24, 26, & 27 ca. Aug., 5 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter, Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker 1878 Aug. 24, APCS (Box 19)
- Alvans Clark to C. S. Venable 1878 Aug. 26, ALS (Box 19)
- J. L. Cabell to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1878 Sept. 9, ALS (Box 19)
- Emma Rogers to Francis H. Smith [1878?] Sept. 11, ALS (Box 19)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1878 Sept. 14, AL (Box 19)
- Eliza (Smith) Walker to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith [1878 Sept. 20], APCS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. Smith (Walker) to father, Francis Harrison Smith 1878 Oct. 4; Nov. 30, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to aunt, Caroline [Harrison] 1878 Oct. 27, ALS (Box 19)
- Ernst Keil to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1878 Nov. 1, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to daughter, Mary Stuart Smith 1878 Nov. 7, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to brother, George Tucker Smith 1878 Nov. 8, ALS (Box 19)
- Edward Buckey to [Eliza L. C. Smith] 1878 Nov. 18, ALS (Box 19)
- Charles C. Harrison to E. L. C. Harrison (mother) 1878 Nov. 25, ALS (Box 19)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1878 Dec. 2, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Caroline H. Harrison 1878 Dec. 12, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellie Smith 1878 Dec. 13, ALS (Box 19)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1878 Dec. 26, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to ellen and Daniel Smith 1879 Jan. 16; March 1; May 16; Aug. 30; Oct. 10, 5 ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to sister, Eleanor A. Smith 1879 Jan. 22; March 10 & 12, 2 ALS, 1 AL, 1 APCS (Box 19)
- Charles A. Smith to F. H. Smith, J. H. Smith and D. G. Smith re: family affairs 1879 Feb. 15-May 25, 4 ALS (Box 19)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to aunt, Caroline E. Harrison 1879 March 11 & May 18, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor A. Smith 189 March 22, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza C. Smith (Walker) to Mrs. E. L. C. Harrison 1879 March 31; April 10; Sept. 14 & 24; Oct. 17; Nov. 10; Dec. 20, 9 ALS, 1 AL (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1879 April 2 & Sept. 22, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith 1879 April 6, ALS (Box 19)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Miss Carrie Harrison 1879 April 7 & 28, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Edward Buckley Smith to Professor F. H. Smith, J. Howard Smith 1879 April 12; May 14 & 21; June 2; Aug. 7 & 19; Sept. 27 & Oct. 11, 9 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 19)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1879 April 19 & Sept. 10, 1 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to mother, Eliza L. C. Harrison 1879 April 21 & Nov. 10, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1879 May 2; July 8 & 9, 1 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 19)
- Frank Stevens to his aunts, Caroline & [Mary Harrison] 1879 June 3 & July 28, ALS (Box 19)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1879 June 4 & Sept. 26, 2 ALS (Box 19)
- Edith M. Thomas to UVA [Professor Kent] 1879 June 5, ALS (Box 19)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1879 June 10, ALS (Box 19)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to aunts, Mary Jane and Caroline Harrison 1879 June 18, ALS (Box 19)
- [?] to Williette (Stevens) Baughman 1879 June 27, AL (Box 19)
- Charles S. Smith to Gessner Harrison Smith 1879 July 5 & 25, ALS (Box 19)
- Francis Harrison Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1879 July 23; Aug. 13, 20, & 27, 4 ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Gessner Harrison Smith 1879 July 23, ALS (Box 19)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to aunt, Caroline Harrison 1879 July [?], ALS (Box 19)
- Gustie S. Duffey to Daniel G. Smith 1879 July [?], ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1879 Aug. 9; [Sept. 3], 1 ALS, 1 APC (Box 19)
- Edward Buckey to Francis H. Smith 1879 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to sister, E[llen E. Smith]1879 Sept. 15, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1879 Sept. 18, ALS (Box 19)
- Francis H. Smith to [Mrs. Daniel Grove Smith 1879 Oct. 3, ALS (Box 19)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellie Smith 1879 Oct. 17, ALS (Box 19)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to her children 1879 Nov. 21, ALS (Box 19)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith 1879 Dec. 8, ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza Smith to Mrs. F. H. Smith (mother) 1879 Dec. 8, ALS (Box 20)
- [Caroline Harrison) to niece, [Lucy R. Harrison] 1879 Dec. 18, AL (Box 20)
- [Eliza L. C. Smith] to sister, Eleanor A. Smith 1879 Dec. 26, AL (Box 20)
- H. W. Murray to Mrs. Lane 1879 Dec. 31, ALS (Box 20)
- Liza L. C. Smith (Walker) to her mother, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 187? April 25 & Aug. 25, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to her Aunt Mary [187?], ALS (Box 20)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Carrie E. Harrison 1880 Jan. 5-Dec. 6, 4 ALS, 4 APCS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker to father, Francis Harrison Smith 1880 Jan. 10 & 29; May 10; July 22, 4 ALS (Box 20)
- Sam S. Wallace to Mary Jane Harrison 1880 Jan. 18, ALS (Box 20)
- F[rancis]; S[mith] to [J.] Howard [Smith] 1880 Jan. 22, ALS (Box 20)
- W. W. Walker to sister-in-law, Eleanor A. Smith 1880 [Jan. 22]; April 1; Oct. 3; 15 & 23, 5 ALS (Box 20)
- [Williette (Stevens) Baughman] to aunts, [Caroline and Mary Jane Harrison] 1880 Jan. 23, AL (Box 20)
- W. W. Walker to grandmother-in-law, (E. L. C. Harrison) 1880 Jan. 24, ALS (Box 20)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith 1880 Jan. 26, ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellie Smith 1880 Jan. 31; March 23; July 5, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Edward Buckley Smith to Professor Francis H. Smith and J. Howard Smith 1880 Jan. 31; Feb. 16; March 24; July 27; Sept. 5, 9, 13; Oct. 11, 14; Dec. 21, ALS (Box 20)
- Nicky Carter to Ellie A. Smith 1880 Feb. 4, ALS (Box 20)
- Caroline E. Harrison to Lucy R. Harrison 1880 Feb. 4, ALS (Box 20)
- Frank Stevens to aunts [Carrie and Mary Harrison] 1880 Feb. 7-Dec. 7, 6 ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1880 Feb. 7 & 17; March 7 & 14; April 16; June 6 & 8; Aug. 21, 8 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Smith) Walker to mother, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1880 Feb. 15; March 16; April 13, 15, 17, 23, 27; Sept. 5, 7 ALS, 1 AL (Box 20)
- J. Howard Smith to F. H. Smith 1880 Feb. 16-Nov. 11, 4 ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to sister, Eleanor A. Smith 1880 Feb. 17; March 12, 25; May 24, June 3, 5 ALS (Box 20)
- Maggie Rice to cousin, Caroline E. Harrison 1880 Feb. 22, ALS (Box 20)
- Williette Stevens (Mrs. Charles C. Baughman) to Mary Jane Harrison 1880 March 1, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Mary F. Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1880 March 4; July 16; Dec. 18, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane and Caroline Harrison [1880?] March 14; Oct. 28, 1 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Mary F. (Mrs. Peachey R.) Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1880 March 20, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. Smith to aunts, Caroline and Mary Jane Harrison 1880 March 25; April 15; May 8; June 3; Sept. 27, 3 ALS, 1 AL, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor F. H. Smith 1880 April 20; July 12; Sept. 6, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to sister, E[llen E. Smith]1880 April 30; Dec. 27, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. Smith 1880 May 3, ALS (Box 20)
- Fannie [?] to Eliza [?] 1880 May 22, ALS (Box 20)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith (later 1st Mrs. Fielding D. Miles, 2nd Mrs. Charles W. Kent) 1880 May 24; July 19; Dec. 3, 2 ALS, 1 AL (Box 20)
- John Singleton Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1880 June 7; Oct. 7, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- M. Peale to [Caroline E. Harrison?] 1880 June 14, ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Eliza L. C. Smith 1880 June 16, 25; Oct. 20, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1880 June 19, ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen [E. Smith] 1880 June 24; Sept. 18; Oct. 25, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Woodrow Wilson to Eleanor A. Smith 1880 June 30, ALS (Box 20)
- Edward S. foyner to Francis H. Smith 1880 July 6, ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Eliza L. C. Smith 1880 July 8, ALS (Box 20)
- John A. Broadus to Mary Stuart Smith 1880 July 10, ALS (Box 20)
- J. L. Cabell to F. H. Smith 1880 July 10-Sept. 4, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- James Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1880 July 12, 29; Sept. 15, 3 ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Stuart Smith and E. H. Rowe to F. H. Smith 1880 July 13-28, 6 ALS, 3 APCS, 1 APC (Box 20)
- Charles S. Venable to [Francis H.] Smith 1880 July 13, ALS (Box 20)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1880 July 16; July 23; Aug. 2; Sept. 6, 4 ALS (Box 20)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt, Mary J. Harrison [ ca. 1880] July 17, ALS (Box 20)
- Francis Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1880 July 21, ALS (Box 20)
- Francis H. Smith to Edward B. Smith, half-brother 1880 July 28, ALS (Box 20)
- Mrs. Virginia Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1880 July 31, ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1880 Aug. 2 & 25, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Juliette Walker to Mrs. Eliza Smith Wallace 1880 Aug. 27, ALS (Box 20)
- W. H. Thornton to Mrs. Daniel Smith 1880 Sept. 2, ALS (Box 20)
- George Tucker Harrison to sister, Mary Harrison 1880 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 20)
- May B. Parham to Ellie Smith 1880 Sept. 5, ALS (Box 20)
- Bella Coleman to Maria F. (Tucker) Rives 1880 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 20)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1880 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 20)
- M. M. Walker to William Thornton 1880 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 20)
- Charles A. Smith to Francis H. Smith and Howard Smith 1880 7 & 8, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- S. S. Steel to Francis H. Smith 1880 Sept. 10, ALS (Box 20)
- Edward Buckey to J. Howard Smith 1880 Sept. 13, ALS (Box 20)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1880 Sept. 14, ALS (Box 20)
- John L. William to Francis H. Smith 1880 Sept. 17, ALS (Box 20)
- A. B. Woodfin to Francis H. Smith 1880 Sept. 17, ALS (Box 20)
- Charles A. Smith to J. Howard Smith 1880 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 20)
- C. [C. Baughman] to Williette (Stevens) Baughman 1880 Sept. 25, ALS (Box 20)
- Peachey Gessner Smith to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith, (sister) 1880 Sept. 25, ALS (Box 20)
- Clara Walker to Ellie [Kent] 1880 Sept. 30, ALS (Box 20)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1880 Dec. 5 & 27, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Caroline E. Harrison to cousin, MaggieRice 1880 Dec. 10, ALS (Box 20)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane and Caroline Harrison [1880?] Dec. 17, ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to [aunt, Mary Jane Harrison] 1880 Dec. 20, ALS (Box 20)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1880 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 20)
- (signature cut away) [Eliza L. C. Smith] to Ellie [Kent], (sister) ca. 1880, AL (Box 20)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Miss Carrie E. Harrison 1881 Jan. 3; March 10, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Mary F. Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1881 Jan. 6, ALS (Box 20)
- Edward Buckley Smith to Professor F. H. Smith and J. Howard Smith 1881 Jan. 11-Dec. 31, 21 ALS, 2 APCS (Box 20)
- Williette Stevens Baughman to aunt, [Caroline and Mary Jane Harrison] 1881 Jan. 25; March 14; April 8; June 13 & Nov. 14, 5 ALS (Box 20)
- Mrs. Ellen E. Smith to Eleanor A. Smith 1881 Jan. 29, ALS (Box 20)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton and William M. Thornton to aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1881 Feb. 27 & Nov. 15, 1 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 20)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to Francis H. Smith 1881 March 9, ALS (Box 20)
- Francis H. Smith to Dr. John A. Broadus 1881 March 12, ALS (Box 20)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor Francis H. Smith 1881 March 14 & 26, 2 ALS (Box 20)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1881 April 7, ALS (Box 20)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1881 April 12; June 8; Aug. 22, 3 ALS (Box 21)
- Bettie [Hamilton Dovall] to Mrs. D. G. Smith 1881 May 1, ALS (Box 21)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt, Mary J. Harrison 1881 May 4 & Sept. 10, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to Mollie [Gentry?] 1881 May 11, ALS (Box 21)
- W. W. Walker to mother and to sister, Lelia 1881 June 10 & 24, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- William B. Rogers to F. H. Smith 1881 June 27, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1881 June 28; July 11-26; Aug. 9-27, 5 ALS, 5 AL, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1881 June 29; July 5-20; Sept. 5-30, 6 ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen [E. Hamilton] 1881 July 2, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith 1881 July 8; Aug. 15-29; Sept. 5-27, 7 ALS, 1 AL, 2 APCS, 1 APC (Box 21)
- [Francis H. Smith] to [Mary Stuart Smith] 1881 July 9, AL (Box 21)
- George Tucker Harrison to nephew, Harvey 1881 July 18, ALS (Box 21)
- [Francis H. Smith] to Rosalie Thornton 1881 July 25, AL (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1881 July 29 & Oct. 14, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1881 Aug. 4, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Rosalie Smith 1881 Aug. 7, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith, Jr. to brother, Gessner Harrison Smith 1881 Aug. [?], ALS (Box 21)
- F[rancis] H. Smith to [Mary Stuart Smith] 1881 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1881 Sept. 13-27, 3 ALS, 3 AL (Box 21)
- G[eorge]; T[ucker] Smith to father 1881 Sept. 22, ALS (Box 21)
- F[rancis] H. Smith to Mrs. [Gessner] Harrison 1881 Sept. 26, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1881 Oct. 7, ALS (Box 21)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith 1881 Oct. 12, ALS (Box 21)
- Edward B. Smith to G. Harrison Smith and Professor F. H. Smith 1881 Nov. 8 & Dec. 24, 2 APCS (Box 21)
- Lelia [Smith] to [Gessner] Harrison [Smith] [1881?], ALS (Box 21)
- R. E. Rogers to Professor F. H. Smith 1882 Jan. 6, ALS (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1882 Jan. 9, 31; may 13; Sept. 2, 4 ALS (Box 21)
- Edward Buckley Smith to Professor F. H. Smith and J. Howard Smith 1882 Jan.-Dec., 23 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Cornelia Rives Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1882 Feb. 6, ALS (Box 21)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Miss Caroline E. Harrison 1882 March 10; May 8, 1 ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- Noah K. Davis to Francis H. Smith w/notes by Francis H. Smith 1882 March 20, ALS (Box 21)
- A. F. Fleet to Francis H. Smith 1882 March 25, ALS (Box 21)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to mother, Eliza L. C. Harrison 1882 April 2; Sept. 5, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor Francis H. Smith 1882 April 10, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1882 April 10; Aug. 12; Nov. 14, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellie A. Smith 1882 April 13, 24; Nov. 13, 3 ALS (Box 21)
- C. W. Kent to R. M. Kent 1882 April 25; Oct. 21, 1 ALS, 1 AL (fragment) (Box 21)
- C. W. Kent to Uncle John 1882 april 28, ALS (Box 21)
- James F. Harrison to C. W. Kent 1882 May 12, ALS (Box 21)
- J. H. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1882 May 12, 15; [June 20]; June 26; July 5; [Dec.?], 3 ALS, 2 AL, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Stuart Smith 1882 May 16, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1882 May 18 & 24; Sept. 7; [Nov. 11], 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- H. T. Kent to Charles W. Kent 1882 May 23, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to brother-in-law J. Howard Smith 1882 June 2, ALS (Box 21)
- Ormond Stowe to Professor F. H. Smith 1882 June 13, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary B. Randolph to Mrs. Gessner Harrison 1882 June 17, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to J. Howard Smith, half-brother 1882 June 27 & 28, 1 ALS, 1 APC (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 July 6-29; Aug. 7 & 11, 5 ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- F[rancis] H. S[mith] to J. Howard Smith 1882 July 13, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 July 20; Aug. 24, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 July 25 & 29; Aug. 2 & 28, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Eleanor Rosalie Smith (Mrs. Carrington Harrison) to brother, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 July 27, ALS (Box 21)
- [Mary Stuart Smith] to [Gessner] Harrison [Smith] 1882 Aug. 1 & 16, 2 AL (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1882 Aug. 2, ALS (Box 21)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1882 Aug. 4 & Sept. 2, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- [George] Tucker [Smith] to Gessner Harrison Smith, (brother) 1882 Aug. 6, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to Rosalie Smith 1882 Aug. 16, ALS (Box 21)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to nephew, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Aug. 21 & 30, 2 ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner H. Smith 1882 Aug. 23 & 31; Sept. 9-23, ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- Francis Harrison Smith and Mary Stuart Smith to Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Aug. 29; Sept. 29; Oct. 2, 25, & 26; Nov. 6, 8, & 18, 6 ALS, 1 AL, 1 APCS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1882 Sept. 8; Nov. 23, 1 ALS, 1 AL (Box 21)
- Henry William Harrison to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1882 Sept. 18, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Sept. 18-27, 4 ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Oct. 2 & 25; Dec. 12, 3 ALS (Box 21)
- [Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith] to son Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Nov. 2, AL (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1882 Nov. 13, 18, & 24, 4 ALS (Box 21)
- Maria T. Rives to [Mrs. Gessner Harrison] 1882 Nov. 29, ALS (Box 21)
- Francis H. Smith to Edward [B. Smith] 1882 Nov. 29, ALS (Box 21)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Dec. 12, ALS (Box 21)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen [E. Smith] 1882 Dec. 27, ALS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 Dec. 31, ALS (Box 21)
- Edward B. Smith to Professor F. H. Smith and J. Howard Smith 1883 Jan. 1-May 22; Aug. 17-23; Nov. 12; Dec. 14, 12 ALS, 1 AL, 2 APCS (Box 21)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1883 Jan. 1, 11, 30; Feb. 22; March 11; April 10, 5 ALS, 1 APC (Box 21)
- Peters et al. to Congress of U. S. re public free schools 1883 Jan. 17, Draft (Box 21)
- Eliza Ridgely Uhler to Ellen [E. Smith] and Mary Harrison 1883 Feb. 3; April 7; Aug. 17, ALS (Box 21)
- William Thornton to Francis H. Smith 1883 Feb. 8, ALS (Box 22)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1883 Feb. 13; March 2, 16; May 14, 24; Nov. 24 & Dec. 22, 7 ALS (Box 22)
- George Tucker Harrison to nephew, Harvey and sister, Mary 1883 Feb. 14; March 12, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- J. H. Smith to brother, Edward Smith 1883 Feb. 18; March 22, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- George Tucker Smith to brother, Gessner Harrison Smith 1883 Feb. 27, ALS (Box 22)
- F[rancis]; S[mith] to J. Howard Smith 1883 March 3, ALS (Box 22)
- Eleanor Rosalie (Harrison) Thornton to Gessner Harrison 1883 March 12, ALS (Box 22)
- Francis Harrison Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1883 March 27; April 24, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1883 April 2; June 14, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Rosalie Smith to Eleanor A. Smith 1883 April 4, ALS (Box 22)
- Eleanor Rosalie Smith (Mrs. Carrington Harrison) to brother, Gessner Harrison Smith 1883 April 4 & 23, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1883 April 9; Sept. 12-29; Oct. 5, 5 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor A. Smith (sister) 1883 April 9 & [1883?], 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1883 April 15; Oct. 3, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to [Gessner] Harrison [Smith] 1883 April 26, ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1883 April 30; May 6 & 8; June 5 & 25, 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to [aunt, Mary Jane Harrison] 1883 May 4, ALS (Box 22)
- Gessner Harrison Smith to father, Francis H. Smith 1883 June 1, ALS (Box 22)
- John L. William to Francis H. Smith 1883 June 15 & 20, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1883 June 29, ALS (Box 22)
- Francis H. Harrison to son, Gessner Harrison Smith [1883] July 18, ALS (Box 22)
- Lelia M. Smith to Eliza Smith 1883 Aug. 26, ALS (Box 22)
- Henry William Harrison to mother [Eliza L. C. T. Harrison] 1883 Aug. 27; Dec. 29, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1883 Sept. 5, 7, 10 & 24, 2 ALS, 2 AL (Box 22)
- [Mary Jane Harrison] to Caroline Harrison 1883 Sept. 10, 1 APCS (Box 22)
- O. G. Clay to [Mary Stuart Harrison] Smith 1883 Sept. 15, ALS (Box 22)
- Rosalie Smith to Eleanor A. Smith (sister) 1883 Sept. 15; Oct. 17; Dec. 3, 3 ALS (Box 22)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison to Ellie A. Smith 1883 Oct. 12; Nov. 12, 24 & 26, 3 ALS, APC (Box 22)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1883 Oct. 13; Dec. 23, 2 ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor A. Smith 1883 Oct. 16; Nov. 11, 3 ALS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1883 Oct. 16; [24], & 28; Nov. 5, 12 & 26, 5 ALS, APCS (Box 22)
- Mary Stuart Smith to aunt, Mary [?] 1883 Oct. 21, ALS (Box 22)